http://www.bbuds.com/privacy-policy

Terms of Service & Privacy Policy
The Terms of Service set forth below (the “Terms”), including the Privacy Policy set forth herein, are the terms and conditions that are applicable to your access and use of each of the websites owned, operated or controlled by Butter Buds Inc. or any of its subsidiaries or affiliates (unless otherwise indicated, collectively referred to as “Butter Buds”, “we” or “us”). Additional terms and conditions may apply to particular areas of the websites (“Website(s)”).
PLEASE READ THESE TERMS CAREFULLY PRIOR TO ACCESSING OR USING THE WEBSITE
By accessing or using the Website, you are accepting the Terms and
agreeing to be legally bound by them. If you do not agree to the Terms,
you are not permitted to access or use the Website. Butter Buds reserves
the right to modify, change, add or remove any or all of the Terms
(including the Privacy Policy and any other terms or conditions relating
to the Website) at any time in its sole discretion, so please
periodically check these Terms for changes. Your continued access to and
use of the Website after Butter Buds posts any such changes constitutes
your consent to the then current Terms.
1. Restrictions on Use of Materials and Access to Website.
Unless otherwise noted on the Website, all content, data, information
and materials available on the Website, including without limitation,
images, illustrations, designs, icons, photographs, video and audio
clips, text and any other content, data, information or materials
(collectively, the “Materials”), are owned by or proprietary to Butter
Buds or its licensors and are protected by applicable intellectual
property laws. Except as expressly authorized by Butter Buds, you agree
not to sell, license, rent, modify, distribute, copy, reproduce,
transmit, publicly display, publicly perform, publish, adapt, edit,
compile or create derivative works of the Materials. You may, however,
download one copy of the Materials on any single computer for your own
internal use only, provided that you retain all copyright and other
proprietary legends on the Materials. Butter Buds reserves all rights to
the Materials, and any other use of the Materials for any purpose not
expressly granted in the Terms or any other applicable written agreement
between Butter Buds and you is expressly prohibited.
2. Trademark Information.
The following is a list of certain trademarks, service marks and/or
trade names owned by or proprietary to us, and we reserve all rights
therein throughout the world. Those marks followed by a ® symbol are
registered trademarks or service marks of BBFI Intellectual Property,
Inc. or CPC Intellectual Property, Inc. in the United States, and
certain of the trademarks or service marks listed may be registered in
other countries or jurisdictions.
SWEET’N LOW®
BUTTER BUDS®
SUGAR IN THE RAW®
NU-SALT®
The following is a list of certain trademarks, service marks and/or
trade names owned by or proprietary to Stadt Holdings Corporation and
used by us under license:
NATRATASTE®
SWEET ONE®
All other trademarks, service marks and trade names used or referenced
on our Website are owned by and reserved to their respective owners.
3. Privacy Policy.
We respect your privacy and provide this Privacy Policy to explain how we treat information you provide to us.
Consent
By using our Website, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure
of your information in the manner disclosed below. Because of the
rapidly evolving legal and business environment surrounding privacy on
the Internet, please be aware that Butter Buds must reserve the right to
modify this Privacy Policy at any time, in which event we would post an
appropriate notice of such change by updating the “Last Updated”
legend.
Please bear in mind that this Privacy Policy only addresses our use
and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that
you disclose information or data to other parties or other websites on
the Internet, including websites that you may reach through our
Websites, different rules or policies may apply.
What Type of Information Do We Collect?
In order to measure the usefulness and efficiency of our Website, and
in an attempt to provide a more pleasant and personalized on-line
experience, we automatically track certain information from all visitors
to our Website. This information is compiled and analyzed on an
aggregated basis.
We may use “cookies” on certain pages of our Website. “Cookies” are
small data files that are stored on your hard drive and contain certain
information accessible to our Website, such as any information content
preferences you may voluntarily set at our Website and your username and
password, if you voluntarily register with us as a user of our Website
(should we at any time make such registration available). You are always
free to turn off cookies if your browser permits, although you may not
be able to use certain features on our Website and you may be required
to reenter your password more frequently during a session if passwords
are required to access any part of our Website.
Butter Buds may also collect information through interactive
questionnaires and registration requests. For example, in response to
such questionnaires and registration requests, you may be asked to
provide (i) your name, (ii) address, (iii) gender, (iv) number of people
in your household or company and their age ranges, and (v) your
preference as to receiving additional information regarding certain
products, services or health related topics. Furthermore, we may request
certain credit card information if you attempt to purchase any products
that may be available from our online stores. Although you are not
required to share such information, if you elect not to share certain
information, you may not be able to purchase certain products and/or
utilize certain services or functionality. If you voluntarily send us
any correspondence, such as emails or letters, we may also retain such
correspondence and information in a file specific to you.
If you have voluntarily provided us with such information, we may use
your email address, mailing address and phone number to contact you
regarding administrative notices, new product offerings and
communications relevant to your use of our Website or products and
services offered by Butter Buds and its affiliates. You have the option
of not participating in these programs by not providing us with your
contact information or by opting out after receipt of such information.
Who Does Butter Buds Share My Information With?
We will not sell, trade, rent or share your personally identifiable
information with any third party, other than as disclosed in this
Privacy Policy and/or unless you consent to such disclosure (e.g., your
request to receive certain goods or services from a third party or
otherwise utilize certain features of the Website, or via direct
agreement to such disclosure). Notwithstanding the above, in order to
offer you a high level of quality products and services, we may use
personally identifiable information or other information you have
provided in order to transmit communications to you, and we may share
certain personally identifiable information about you with our
subsidiaries, affiliates, agents and partners. Butter Buds takes all
reasonable precautions to ensure that its subsidiaries, affiliates,
agents and partners respect the privacy of your personally identifiable
information and use it only for its intended purposes. You may opt-out
of any disclosure of your personally identifiable information by sending
a blank e-mail message to opt-out@bbuds.com.
We may use some third party suppliers and providers to directly or
indirectly provide products and services to our customers, and we may
need to share your personally identifiable information with them in
order to permit them to provide the products and services. For example,
we use a reputable third party credit card processing agency for online
purchases made with credit cards. If you choose to use these optional
services or products, we will, by necessity, provide some of your
personally identifiable information to the third party provider offering
such services or products for purposes consistent with such offering.
Additionally, in some instances, the third party supplier or provider
may collect information directly from you. Because we do not control the
privacy practices of these third parties, you should evaluate their
practices before deciding to use their services or products. In
addition, a co-brand provider may directly ask you for certain
information to assist it in providing you with products or services.
Butter Buds expressly reserves the right to retain, disclose or
report any of your information in limited circumstances where we
reasonably deem it necessary to comply with applicable laws, rules and
regulations, to cooperate with government or industry regulators and law
enforcement officials, to perform any necessary credit checks or
collect or report debts owed to us, or to protect our rights or
property. It is our policy to comply with any such requirements
(including a good-faith belief that such requirement exists), and you
agree we shall have no liability for any such disclosure or retention.
We also may collect and report to third parties aggregate,
non-personally identifiable information about you and other users of our
Website for advertising, marketing and promotional purposes.
What Kinds of Security Procedures Does Butter Buds Use?
We use industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of
your personal identifiable information, such as firewalls and Secure
Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption if your browser is capable of using such
encryption. However, please bear in mind that “perfect security” does
not exist on the Internet, although you can increase your protection by
proper use and maintenance of your passwords, electing to use SSL or
industry standard encryption when available and evaluating the privacy
policies of websites you use.
A Special Note on Children
Pursuant to the terms of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act
(COPPA), we do not knowingly collect personally-identifiable
information from children under the age of thirteen (13). The Website is
not directed at children under the age of thirteen (13), and by using
the Website and/or providing information to us, you represent that you
are not under the age of thirteen 13).
What should I do if I have questions?
If you would like us to update, change, or delete any personally
identifiable information we have about you (subject to any applicable
legal exceptions), would like to opt out of receiving further
information, or have questions about our privacy policy, please contact
us at privacy.policy@bbuds.com. You may also write, call or fax us at:
Privacy Policy, Butter Buds Inc., 2330 Chicory Road, Racine, WI 53403.
T: 262-598-9900 F: 262-598-9999.
4. Links to Other Sites.
Any third-party links and applications in or on our Website are
subject to such third party’s separate and independent privacy policies
and terms of use, and we have no responsibility or liability for the
content and activities of such linked sites or applications. We
recommend that you review all applicable third party privacy policies
before you disclose personal information.
5. Disclaimer of Warranties and Limitation of Liability.
THE WEBSITE, THE MATERIALS AND ANY PRODUCTS OR SERVICES AVAILABLE ON
ORACCESSIBLE THROUGH THE WEBSITE ARE PROVIDED “AS
IS,” AND NEITHER BUTTER BUDS NORANY OF ITS SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES OR SUPPLIERS MAKES ANY REPRESENTATIONS ORWARRANTIES WITH RESPECT TO ANY OF THE FOREGOING. BUTTER BUDS SPECIFICALLYDISCLAIMS ANY OTHER WARRANTY, EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY, INCLUDING ANYWARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR WARRANTYAGAINST INFRINGEMENT. NEITHER BUTTER BUDS NOR ANY OF ITS SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES ORSUPPLIERS IS UNDER ANY OBLIGATION TO UPDATE ANY MATERIALS OR CONTINUE TO OFFER ANYMATERIALS, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES CURRENTLY AVAILABLE ON THE WEBSITE. ACCESS TO THEWEBSITE, ANY OF THE MATERIALS, AND ANY PRODUCTS OR SERVICES AVAILABLE ON
ORACCESSIBLE THROUGH THE WEBSITE MAY BE LIMITED OR UNAVAILABLE AT ANY TIME,INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DURING PERIODS OF PEAK DEMAND, SYSTEM UPGRADES,MALFUNCTIONS,
OR SCHEDULED OR UNSCHEDULED MAINTENANCE OR FOR OTHER REASONS.
THE PACKAGING INGREDIENTS AND OTHER CLAIMS REFERENCED ON THE WEBSITES APPLYSOLELY TO PRODUCTS DISTRIBUTED IN THE UNITED STATES, AND SHALL NOT APPLY TOPRODUCTS SOLD OR DISTRIBUTED OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES.
IN
NO EVENT WILL BUTTER BUDS, ANY OF ITS SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES OR SUPPLIERS OROTHER PERSONS TRANSMITTING THE MATERIALS BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANYONE ELSE FOR ANYCONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR INDIRECT DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITEDTO, LOST PROFITS, TRADING LOSSES AND DAMAGES THAT MAY RESULT FROM THE USE OF THEMATERIALS OR ANY PRODUCTS SOLD VIA THE WEBSITE,
OR FROM INCONVENIENCE, DELAY ORLOSS OF USE OF THE MATERIALS OR FOR OMISSIONS OR INACCURACIES IN THE MATERIALS ORFROM LOSS OR CORRUPTION OF DATA OR THE COST OF RECOVERING ANY DATA) EVEN IFADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES AND,
AS
A CONDITION TO ACCESSING SUCHMATERIALS, YOU EXPRESSLY WAIVE ANY CLAIM YOU MAY HAVE AGAINST BUTTER BUDS, ANY OFITS SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES OR SUPPLIERS,
OR ANY OTHER PERSON WITH RESPECT TO ANYMATERIALS, OR PORTION THEREOF.
6. Termination.
Butter Buds reserves the right to terminate your use of and/or access
to the Website and any or all of the Materials or any portion thereof
without any liability to you and to take any other action Butter Buds
deems appropriate, in its sole discretion, without limitation for any
reason whatsoever.
7. Miscellaneous.
Governing Law. These Terms shall be governed by and construed in
accordance with the laws of the State of Wisconsin, without regard to
its conflicts of laws provisions. All disputes arising out of or with
respect to the Terms shall be heard exclusively in the federal and state
courts of the state of Wisconsin, and each of the parties hereto
expressly consents and submits to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue
of such courts, unless Butter Buds chooses to bring suit in an
alternative location. No Waiver. Our failure to exercise or enforce any
right or provision of the Terms shall not constitute a waiver of such
right or provision. If any provision of these Terms shall be unlawful,
void, or for any reason unenforceable, that provision shall be deemed
severable from these Terms and shall not affect the validity and
enforceability of any remaining provisions. These Terms, and any web
pages or other documents or policies incorporated by reference, set
forth the entire understanding and agreement between us with respect to
the subject matter hereof.
California Shine the Light Law. Under California’s “Shine the Light”
law, California residents who provide personal information in obtaining
products or services for personal, family or household use are entitled
to request and obtain from us, once per calendar year, information about
the customer information we shared, if any, with other businesses for
their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information would
include the categories of customer information and the names and
addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information
for the immediately prior calendar year (e.g., requests made in 2012
will receive information regarding 2011 sharing activities). To obtain
this information from us, please email us at privacy.policy@bbuds.com
and enter “Request for California Privacy Information” for the subject
of your message, and we will send you a reply e–mail containing the
requested information. Not all information sharing is covered by the
“Shine the Light” requirements and only information on covered sharing
will be included in our response.
